Here's a dog object from earlier as well as the invokeTwice function.
يوجد كائن "dog" من السابق إضافة إلى الدالة "invokeTwice".
Just to recap, we tried calling invokeTwice and passed in dog.growOneYear,
ولمجرد تلخيص ذلك، حاولنا استدعاء "invokeTwice" وتمريرها في "dog.growOneYear"،
but that actually returned undefined.
ولكن رجع غير محدد بالفعل.
To solve this, we can now use the bind method which
لحل هذا، يمكن أن نستخدم الآن أسلوب "bind"
returns a new function with the value of this correctly bound.
الذي يقوم بإرجاع دالة جديدة مع قيمة هذه الدالة "bound" بطريقة صحيحة.
Now, bind is a method that we can call directly onto a function, so let's do that.
الآن، "bind" عبارة عن أسلوب يمكننا استدعاؤه مباشرة إلى الدالة، لنفعل ذلك.
Now, let's go ahead and pass in an argument into bind that'll serve as
لنتقدم الآن ونقوم بتمرير وسيطة في "bind" التي ستعمل
the this parameter for the target function which
مثل المعلمة "this" للدالة المستهدفة
is growOneYear when the bound function is called.
وهي "growOneYear" عندما يتم استدعاء الدالة "bound".
In this case, we don't want this to be the global object or window,
في هذه الحالة، لا نريد أن يكون ذلك الكائن العام أو النافذة،
which is the case when we called invokeTwice up here.
وهي الحالة عندم نقوم باستدعاء "invokeTwice" بالأعلى هنا.
We actually want this to be dog because we want
ونريد حقًا أن يكون ذلك "dog" لأننا نريد
the dog's age to increase by one. Let's go ahead and do that.
زيادة عمر "dog" بمعدل واحد. لنتابع ونفعل هذا.
The return value of this is a new function.
قيمة الإرجاع لهذا هي دالة جديدة.
So, let's go ahead and save this to a new variable.
لذلك، لنتابع ونقوم بحفظ ذلك في متغير جديد.
We'll call it myGrow.
وسنطلق عليه "myGrow".
Great. Now, we can pass myGrow into invokeTwice.
رائع. الآن، يمكننا تمرير المتغير "myGrow" إلى الدالة "invokeTwice".
So, what this function invokeTwice just did was that it called myGrow twice,
وما فعلته هذه الدالة "invokeTwice" كان ما يُسمى "&lt;b&gt;myGrow twice"،&lt;/b&gt;
as we can see over here.
كما نرى هنا.
Now, if we access the dog's age property,
والآن إذا أمكننا الوصول إلى خاصية "age" للكائن "dog"،
we should see an updated value.
فإننا يجب أن نرى قيمة مُحدَّثة.
And indeed, it's true, seven.
وبالفعل، هذا صحيح، سبعة.
Just to recap, bind is a method that we call directly onto
ولتلخيص ذلك، "bind" هو أسلوب نقوم باستدعائه مباشرة إلى
a function and returns a copy of that function with a specified this value.
دالة ونقوم بإرجاع نسخة من هذه الدالة مع هذه القيمة المحددة.